Guide to the Paul Jablonski Videotapes of the Cherry Bowl Volleyball Tournament
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Paul Jablonski videotapes of the Cherry Bowl Volleyball Tournament
1984-1994
MS 1902
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.55
12.5
The collection comprises digital video files made from videotapes documenting the Cherry Bowl Volleyball Tournament, an annual charity beach volleyball tournament, begun in 1984, pitting the Cherry Grove Grovettes against various emergency services and police departments from the Long Island and New York City area.
Jablonski, Paul
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Paul Jablonski, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Paul Jablonski is a summer resident of Cherry Grove (Long Island), New York. He has been an active member of the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender community there, organizing annual events such as the Cherry Grove LGBT Pride Parade and coordinating the Cherry Grove Chamber of Commerce.
Scope and Contents
The collection comprises digital video files made from videotapes documenting the Cherry Bowl Volleyball Tournament, an annual charity beach volleyball tournament, begun in 1984, pitting the Cherry Grove Grovettes against various emergency services and police departments from the Long Island and New York City area.
Arrangement
The video file descriptions are arranged chronologically.
Cherry Grove (N.Y.); Fire Island (N.Y.: Island); LGBTQ resource; Jablonski, Paul
- Computer files (Box 1U–7U)
- 1984, 6 computer files (DVD-Video)
  General note
  Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
- 1985, 1987, 7 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 2U)
- 1988, 7 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 3U)
- 1991, 8 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 4U)
- 1993, 7 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 5U)
- 1994, 8 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 6U)
- Cherry Bowl clips, Circa 1984-circa 1994; 7 computer files (DVD-Video)
  - Use copy, 1 (Box 7U)